fantom-xp.org 2015-03-14

# Privacy policies

### Privacy Policy for the Website.

Last Updated: March 21, 2009

This privacy policy describes how the website, collects and uses information from users. The Yield Manager Site is the web-based user interface for the technology. This site is used primarily by Right Media and its customers, and their employees and agents.

We collect Web usage information when Web visitors access our Web sites, including IP address, Web browser and operating system types, Web pages visited on our Web sites, time spent on our Web pages, and return visits to our Web sites. We may combine Web usage information with personal identifying information. We comply with all applicable laws and regulations, including the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

How we use cookies, Web beacons, etc.

* Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that a Web server sends to your computer when you visit a Web site. Cookies can contain a variety of information, such as a simple count of how often you visit a Web site or information that allows us to customize our Web site for your use. Web beacons (also known as "clear gifs" or "one-pixel gifs") are small graphic images on a Web page that allow us to monitor the activity on our Web sites or to make cookies more effective.  
* We, may use "cookies" to tailor and improve the content we deliver to our Web visitors, to improve our Web sites by assessing which areas, features, and products are most popular, and to personalize our Web sites and make recommendations based on information, including product choices, a particular visitor has previously provided. For example, we may use a cookie to identify your state so we do not ask you to enter it more than once. We also use cookies to store user preferences.

* You can configure your Web browser to alert you when a Web site is attempting to send a cookie to your computer and allow you to accept or refuse the cookie. You can also set your browser to disable the capacity to receive cookies or you can delete cookies previously accepted. Some Web pages (and other Web pages) may not work correctly if you have cookies disabled.  
* We may use advertising companies to deliver ads for offered services and products on our Web sites or on third party Web sites. These Internet ads are often called "banner ads" and may contain third-party cookies or Web beacons that allow tracking of visitors' responses to our advertisements. Although these third parties may receive anonymous Web usage information about ad viewing on such Web sites, we prohibit them from using this information for any purpose other than to assist us in measuring the effectiveness of our ads.  
* We may also accept third party advertisements on our Web sites. You should refer to the privacy policy of these advertisers for information regarding their use of cookies and collection of information. You can visit the Network Advertising Initiative Web site to opt out of certain network advertisers' cookies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

* * *

Advertising companies: 

DoubleClick’s Privacy Policy  
http://emea.doubleclick.com/UK/privacy/default.aspx

DoubleClick’s FAQ  
http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx

DoubleClick’s DART Ad-Serving and Search Cookie Opt-Out  
http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

Yield Manager Privacy Policy  
http://content.yieldmanager.com/privacy.html

W3i Privacy Policies  
http://www.w3i.com/privacy_policies.aspx
